Let us talk about one of the exfiltration tools that was developed by the threat actors
to exfiltrate the data into the cloud applications.
So, we have seen the R clone that was commonly released with the detectors to deliver their
sensitive files into their cloud. But sometimes if the threat actor needs to perform
the exfiltration thing in very, very silent way because if the earlier organizations
are a company created an application control policy or created a rule for a R clone detection
crew for an R clone.exe, it will be easily get detected by antivirus officers or e-mail
platforms.
So, instead of going through the R clone.exe, the threat actor's plan to create their
own exfiltration executable. But only some time, only a few threat actors used this
steel bit exfiltration tools to exfiltrate the data. So, the log did and they have used
the steel bit cool for an exfiltration. So, this is developed by the threat actors. So,
it will exfiltrate the data from the machine. So, if you think about the R clone. So,
maybe you will be feeling only R clone will be used by threat actors for an exfiltration
not that scenario. They will be using their own executable to exfiltrate the data. So, this
is also enough for the important things we need to notify, we need to monitor or we need
to do some analysis in this. So, maybe in future, now it is a steel bit, maybe in future
the other application will be also coming. And other things I have let us discuss about
the other things in the next video. Let us hope of from here and we will continue our
discussion and next video. See you guys. Bye.